{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088773054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088773054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088777672","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088777671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088784486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088784486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088788688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088788688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088793258","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088793257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088797356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088797356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088801407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088801407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088805586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088805586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088810761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088810761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088815196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088815195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088820993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088820993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 60b6e4fc-4916-428a-aca1-4bb5f662d67c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088830042","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088830042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" e9afac49-b629-478e-bab2-e543cf5ad5e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088830059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088830058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" e9afac49-b629-478e-bab2-e543cf5ad5e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088830194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088830193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" e9afac49-b629-478e-bab2-e543cf5ad5e7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088841315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088841315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088841705","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088841704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088841946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088841946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088842270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088842270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088842523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088842523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088846318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088846318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088846612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088846612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088847517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088847517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088847957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088847957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088851638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088851638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088851932","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088851932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088852800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088852799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088853473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088853473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088854213","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088854213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088854551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088854551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088854833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088854833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088855161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088855161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088855432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088855432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088859108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088859108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088859508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088859508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088859759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088859759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088860086","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088860086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088860337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088860337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088863802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088863801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088864103","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088864103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088865016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088865013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088865447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088865447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088868475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088868475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088868767","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088868766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088869615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088869615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088870281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088870281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088871023","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088871021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088871361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088871361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088871649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088871649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088871977","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088871976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088872261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088872260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088875731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088875730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088875840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088875840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088885181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088885180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088899920","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088899920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 465697fc-3125-4216-8fc0-ae3cd68bc154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088917415","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088917415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-ma-kwe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088921890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088921890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_msta-da-mlo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088926954","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088926954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_zo-ze-da"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088931063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088931063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-kha-vo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088935380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088935380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-mwi-kwi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088939875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088939875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_sa-mti-da"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088948859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088948859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_sa-mti-da"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088953656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088953656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_va-mcho-da"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088958332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088958332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_mka-da-mwe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" mwe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088965888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088965888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_mka-da-mwe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088969903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088969903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_nji-da-ru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088977819","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088977819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_nji-da-ru"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088981986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088981986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_vya-da-chi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088988282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088988280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_da_vya-da-chi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088994476","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088994475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" dfa93495-23a2-4d80-b900-684a41cd24c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_da_vya-da-chi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089011959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089011959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-kha-vo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089016557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089016556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-ma-kwe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089021239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089021239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_sa-mti-da"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089028476","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089028475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_zo-ze-da"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089033936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089033936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_va-mcho-da"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089041711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089041711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_vya-da-chi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089046549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089046548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-mwi-kwi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089052347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089052347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_msta-da-mlo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089057644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089057644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_mka-da-mwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089061841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089061841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_nji-da-ru"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089067667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089067667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 32b2938e-cb53-4c50-8619-afea1b328667"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_da_nji-da-ru"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089085596","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089085595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" ad5bf4c5-258c-4cb7-9fcf-acb9fc48bb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089096523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089096522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" ad5bf4c5-258c-4cb7-9fcf-acb9fc48bb90"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089107290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089107290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 63d5802a-20c6-45e0-bec6-d99a0ba45f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" da"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DA"," userResponse":" DA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089110324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089110323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 63d5802a-20c6-45e0-bec6-d99a0ba45f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" da"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089111289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089111289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 63d5802a-20c6-45e0-bec6-d99a0ba45f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" de"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" DE"," userResponse":" DA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089111884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089111884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 63d5802a-20c6-45e0-bec6-d99a0ba45f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" de"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DE"," userResponse":" DE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089160377","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089160377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 63d5802a-20c6-45e0-bec6-d99a0ba45f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" de"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089160631","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089160631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" 63d5802a-20c6-45e0-bec6-d99a0ba45f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" de"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DE"," userResponse":" DE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089170246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089170246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" cf14478b-6343-4dd5-a964-64f79f57b013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089170279","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089170278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" cf14478b-6343-4dd5-a964-64f79f57b013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089170528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089170527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" cf14478b-6343-4dd5-a964-64f79f57b013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.da..du.asc.lc.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089179427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089179427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" cf14478b-6343-4dd5-a964-64f79f57b013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089186842","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089186841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" cf14478b-6343-4dd5-a964-64f79f57b013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549089193313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549089193313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_092601"," gameId":" cf14478b-6343-4dd5-a964-64f79f57b013"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}